<resources>
    <string name="app_name">hremp</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">
    Thank you for using our Employee and HR Application. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, and protect your personal information.

    <b>1. Information We Collect:</b>
    - Personal Information: We may collect personal information such as your name, email address, and other relevant details.
    - Usage Data: We collect information about how you interact with our application, including pages visited, features used, and other usage patterns.

    <b>2. How We Use Your Information:</b>
    - Personalization: We use your information to personalize your experience within the application.
    - Communication: We may use your email address to send important updates, announcements, and newsletters.

    <b>3. Data Security:</b>
    We prioritize the security of your data and implement measures to safeguard it against unauthorized access and disclosure.

    <b>4. Third-Party Services:</b>
    Our application may utilize third-party services for analytics and other purposes. These services have their own privacy policies, and we recommend reviewing them.

    <b>5. User Rights:</b>
    You have the right to access, correct, or delete your personal information. For assistance, please contact our support team.

    <b>6. Changes to Privacy Policy:</b>
    We may update this Privacy Policy as needed. You will be notified of any significant changes.

    By using our application, you agree to the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy.

    For any questions or concerns regarding your privacy, please contact us at [your_contact_email@example.com].
</string>

    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_content">
    Welcome to our Employee and HR Application. By accessing or using our application, you agree to abide by these Terms of Service.

    <b>1. Acceptance of Terms:</b>
    By using our application, you agree to comply with these Terms of Service. If you do not agree, please refrain from using our services.

    <b>2. Use of the Application:</b>
    You are granted a limited, non-exclusive, and non-transferable license to use our application for its intended purpose.

    <b>3. User Responsibilities:</b>
    - You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account credentials.
    - You agree not to engage in any unlawful activities or activities that may harm the integrity of our application.

    <b>4. Intellectual Property:</b>
    The content, features, and functionality of the application are protected by intellectual property laws. Unauthorized use may violate copyright and other laws.

    <b>5. Termination of Services:</b>
    We reserve the right to terminate or suspend your access to the application without prior notice if you violate these Terms of Service.

    <b>6. Limitation of Liability:</b>
    We are not liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, or punitive damages arising from your use of the application.

    <b>7. Changes to Terms:</b>
    We may update these Terms of Service from time to time. It is your responsibility to review the terms periodically. Continued use of the application constitutes acceptance of any changes.

    <b>8. Governing Law:</b>
    These Terms of Service are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of [your jurisdiction].

    <b>9. Contact Information:</b>
    For questions or concerns regarding these Terms of Service, please contact us at [your_contact_email@example.com].

    By using our application, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these Terms of Service.
</string>


</resources>